<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Esoteric Plutocrat</title>
        <description>Unravel the mysticism of intuition</description>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
        <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self"
        type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 19:13:26 +0530</pubDate>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 19:13:26 +0530</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
        
        <item>
            <title>The benevolent talisman </title>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;She has the wizardry to disrupt the havoc of mediocrity and transform it into something eternal, to the pinnacle of brilliance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You could keep listening to her sweet and melodious voice for eternity and still crave for more. It’s not about what she says, it’s about how she says it. She has an innate gift of charismatic persuasion. She is the queen of benevolence. She is a talisman who teaches me the moral norms, the indispensable fallacies of life. The respect and love I have for her is invaluable. I could bet my life for her. No, she ain’t my infatuation or a high-school sweetheart. She’s Ruks, Miss Rukhsheen Vajifdar, the goddess of vivacity and the mistress of flamboyance. The person with the most benevolent heart, and indeed a beautiful mind. She’s my precious sensei.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“ They say people come, they say people go but this particular diamond is extra special. ”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She is gorgeous, charming, magnanimous… just so perfect. I know I had a crush on her since the first time I saw her. I felt an intuitive connection with her. I was very attentive and interested in English, the subject she taught, not only due to her but I also have a natural fascination towards the language. We developed a very good rapport ever since. . She was charismatic and completely indulged into teaching. She is passionate about teaching and she really loves it. So far the best professor I’ve ever encountered. I feel that our wavelengths tune in. She is my favourite person. I had even considered to switch to English as a career due to the esoteric aura she radiated. She turned that obnoxious and dull environment into an Elysium, full of euphoria and bliss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The wrath of her grandeur is calamitous  &lt;br /&gt;
Zenith of exquisite just like Aphrodite&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Diligence that of a honey badger, &lt;br /&gt;
ceaseless endeavours longing for passion and contentment&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Possesses a charm of intelligence just like Athena &lt;br /&gt;
An innate knack to inculcate wisdom  &lt;br /&gt;
Possesses an Intuitive persona which unravels the mystic revelations of life &lt;br /&gt;
Benevolent heart as clear and as a crystal  &lt;br /&gt;
and as prodigious as the ocean&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her vivacious persona is a glimpse into her benevolent and eternal soul&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Her aura, par excellence…  &lt;br /&gt;
Words are deceptive, abstract and generalised incompatible with feelings  &lt;br /&gt;
A colossal dilemma for mankind…  &lt;br /&gt;
Humans have become linguistic.  &lt;br /&gt;
An omnipresent barrier between what we feel and what we say    &lt;br /&gt;
Nevertheless I’ll endeavour to unravel her charisma:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mysticism is surreal  &lt;br /&gt;
Delightful yet esoteric &lt;br /&gt;
Overawed and thrilled by the intensity of her vibes &lt;br /&gt;
Her presence illuminates your persona   &lt;br /&gt;
Elevating you to the pinnacle of excellence &lt;br /&gt;
Her fierce aura radiates a flamboyant vibe&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
            <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 17:42:12 +0530</pubDate>
            <link>http://localhost:4000#/2018/03/18/benevolent-talisman.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000#/2018/03/18/benevolent-talisman.html</guid>
            
            
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
